He is currently in a sleep state.
He wakes up sitting up cross-legged,
stays awake for a few hours,
then falls asleep for another 24 hours.
It's all understandable.
His entire memory is gone, after all.
How is he retaining new information
since getting resuscitated?
It's normal.
He has learned about
30 English words so far.
However,
he does not comprehend his identity.
Even his family…
He doesn't show any response,
even to his daughter's photos.
His brain waves and EKG are
within normal parameters.
But his muscle mass has decreased.
With all his memories gone,
he does not feel any reason to live,
causing the body to rapidly atrophy.
What can we do, Doctor?
I cannot say.
His only chance of recovery might be
retrieving his memory.
Doctor, do not touch his head!
He got hurt!
We must treat him!
I'm sorry, Doctor. I forgot to warn you.
Did he use his Stand just now?
He did. However,
that wasn't from his consciousness.
It was just his instinctive bodily reflex
to defend.
"Jo… Lyne."
"Jolyne"?
No… that's not possible.
I've always…
I've always cared about you.
Something's going on with your cut.
It was fixed. I know I just filled it in.
It looks like some sort of writing,
doesn't it?
Should I try to fill it again?
Wait.
Don't fill this one.
I can't explain it, but…
I just know it.
This is a message from my father.
He's had so much to protect
even before I was born.
He was always away to keep dangers
like the one I'm in now
away from me and Mom.
I felt it, just now.
My body tells me that
I understand my father now.
EPISODE 19: BIRTH OF THE "GREEN"
- Hey F.F.
- What?
Can you trip Jolyne down the stairs?
Just a little bit will do.
Why would I do that?
I said, try to trip her.
We won't let her get hurt, of course.
I want to catch her from falling
with my own arms.
What?
Jolyne doesn't seem like
she understood that I saved her.
I want to embrace her tightly
one more time.
Now, get to it.
- Trip her.
- Why don't you do it?
That's sexual harassment.
I already told you.
I'm going to marry Jolyne.
And you promised to cooperate.
Or do you not keep your word?
Now, go do it.
I'm sorry, Jolyne.
The small man!
He's right here!
He was spying on us from above!
Look! He has the bone in his hand!
This fucker sure moves in a funny way,
but he won't get away!
Hold it!
Do you see his back contorting?
You called him a small man.
It's true he fit the description earlier.
- But something strange is happening…
- Sunbathing…
Isn't he growing taller?
He's as tall as me,
no, he's taller than me now.
You have nowhere to run.
Turn around slowly.
The sunlight is nice and warm.
Light is good.
I said turn around, you little shit!
Bleh…
Bleh.
What the fuck is with him?
Light, bleh, warm.
We are happy… as we gather around…
and it's warm.
Bleh.
What was that?
Did you see that stuff splatter?
He could be a Stand User!
Keep your distance.
It doesn't seem to be a Stand.
I don't know what it is,
but we mustn't touch him.
Where's the bone?
The bone he had earlier. Where is it now?
What the…
The other prisoners
have already fallen prey.
Those look like plants.
They're still growing.
What happened to them, and who did this?
What is the meaning of this?
Should I assume that it's a Stand ability?
This bone,
along with the power and some sort of will
that sprouted these plants…
It's as if they are trying to
give birth to something.
It bloomed the flowers first,
then the plants matured.
They grew out at
the end of the person's life.
Now, what to do with this bone
that the man dropped…
Merely touching this bone
or anyone who grabbed it
can be dangerous, after all.
Don't take another step, Jolyne Cujoh!
Stop right there!
Show me your face.
Turn around.
- What?
- It's nothing.
I want to take a moment to
check something.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Let go of her, asshole!
F.F., you stay silent.
The bone transformed the prisoners
in the Disciplinary Wing into that state.
It can't be an enemy Stand,
since that would have
targeted us from the start.
And if I'm not mistaken, Jolyne,
I think I saw your thread touching
that bone when it was still in his grasp.
The bone! It's rolling away!
She's infected!
Jolyne!
But how?
Diver Drive!
Yes!
Weed them all out from the inside, quick!
There's more!
Why did you stop?
I wouldn't exactly say they're growing out
of her or that they need to be rooted out.
Rather, her body itself
is transforming into plants.
Is it safe to pull them out?
Jolyne, does it hurt?
No.
I guess I did touch that bone.
Anyway, you should stay away from me
now that I'm infected.
It might spread to you.
These are just plants,
nothing more, nothing less.
I can't tell what species they are,
but its stems are filled
with chlorophyll, not blood.
Either way,
I'll take care of it. I promise.
The sunlight!
Get in the shade.
If you touch sunlight
or move toward the light,
the plants will grow rapidly.
Step farther into the shade,
and the plants recede.
Damn, what does it want?
I can't say,
but I still need to get that bone.
And just how will you do that?
If you hold the bone,
you'll turn into a plant, Jolyne!
I will pick it up.
I'm already becoming a plant.
Don't go where
the sunlight touches, Jolyne!
The bone… Where is it?
Where can it be?
I thought I saw it rolling
towards this flower.
A star shape?
What is this bruise-like mark?
It's see-through.
There's something else underneath.
A child…
It's a green child!
STAND NAME: YA-YA MA
STAND MASTER: D AN' G
What is it shaped like?
Carrots that look like Snoopy,
breast-shaped radishes, and other shapes
are found all the time during harvests.
This is just like those.
It really just resembles a child.
It's alive! Impossible!
Jolyne, forget about it and come back!
Haven't you noticed?
Your legs are turning too.
They are attaching to the vines!
What is this thing?
Is it a plant, or is it a human?
It turned the prisoners
in the Disciplinary Wing into plants,
joined their roots, and became a fruit!
The bone must have gotten
implanted inside this fruit.
Pale Snake is at this prison
to discover what lies beyond this point.
What will it spawn?
He wants to know
what transpires when it is born.
I told you to come back, Jolyne.
The sun is moving westward,
causing more sunlight to enter.
You must move further back.
Are you taking that with you?
We call this seizing by force, F.F.
I will not let Pale Snake have it.
Come, Jolyne.
We must move opposite the sun's direction.
Anastasia.
This wing's entrance is to the west.
We'll never leave this shitty place
if we go east.
There's at least one other Stand User
somewhere in this wing.
Escape, huh.
Help me, please.
Someone help!
Please!
After everyone drowned, they turned
into plants and died! How horrible!
I'm begging you!
I don't want to turn into a plant!
Please, get me out of here!
Fine.
What's your name? Are you hurt?
What are you saying, Anastasia?
He could be our enemy.
Are they right? Are you against us?
I don't know what you are talking about.
My name is Guccio.
I just don't want to turn into a plant!
Calm down. I said it's fine.
Stand up, Guccio.
Surely you can do that much.
Now hurry it up.
Do you know this?
A human has 12 pairs of ribs,
or 24 bones in total.
Whether a man or a woman, tall or short,
we all have the same number of ribs.
Good. Now go.
I guess he wasn't our enemy after all.
I couldn't care less either way.
I'm only interested
in safely leaving through
the east side of this building.
Isn't that right?
The keyword is "safely."
Let's leave from there.
A green child…
I wasn't told about any of this,
but my job is simple.
Finish off Jolyne Cujoh.
Just that, and nothing more.
I will merely complete my assignment.
Where are they?
Where did Jolyne Cujoh
and her two allies go?
Have they already left the building?
No, they cannot leave without me knowing.
Hey you, what are you doing there?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Where did those three go?
And how did you manage
to avoid becoming a plant?
Walk… outside…
- Save me…
- How terrible.
Someone restructured his body
into a human trap!
Fuck, it hurts!
Mommy, it hurts!
I don't want this shitty arm anymore!
I got screwed.
I'm only here
because Pale Snake ordered me
to cause a fight in here
with my Survivor Stand.
But forget that now.
I'm finally outside now.
GUCCIO
STAND NAME: SURVIVOR - BEYOND RECOVERY
Anyway, it looks like we got away
from the other Stand User.
The plants withered away.
I guess it was a temporary bloom.
The problem is that it's about time
for someone from the prison
to realize the abnormalities
going on in the Disciplinary Wing.
That works in our favor.
Once that happens,
then Pale Snake will realize it too.
He will appear close to us.
This is the best chance yet of
getting my father's disc back.
Jolyne, watch out!
Stone Ocean!
It's an enemy Stand!
He must belong to that
gladiator-looking man!
He swallowed the fruit!
I won't let them have it!
Asshole!
Diver Drive!
What is up with his body?
He stinks… really bad!
Go deeper, please!
- Shit, my Stand can't enter it!
- Punish me more, please!
I can feel it through my Stand!
My body's starting to stink
from the inside!
Those shoes of yours.
Did my bodily liquid dirty them?
I am very sorry.
Now please, come sit on this chair.
Let me lick your shoes clean.
Would you like this comic book?
I lifted it from the guards' break room.
Careful, there's a bee.
My master is named D an' G.
The last I saw of him,
he was in the Disciplinary Wing.
His right arm got ripped off
and he was crying for his mommy.
It's a remotely controlled Stand!
He wants to take the fruit to his User!
Shit, they've noticed.
The guards are coming!
Jolyne, we must leave for now.
Let's go toward the wetlands.
There must be a water bike
or a boat somewhere close.
This is how to tell wild
strawberries apart.
The ones with yellow flowers
are mock strawberries, so don't eat them.
Shut your annoying trap.
We can't leave this Stand alone.
We need to find a way to get
that green child out of its belly.
I know that.
F.F., we have no choice but to take it.
We'll leave you to find its User
and finish him off.
Got it.
Oh, you want me to go with you, Master.
This boat here is built specifically
for the wetlands, Master.
It has a propeller engine,
and it uses wind to propel forward.
Shit, how do I start the ignition?
Is there a lock somewhere?
It's a throttle lever, Master.
Usually, it must be put
in neutral first, like this.
This stick is for steering.
Push it forward to turn
the empennage to the right,
and pull the stick back
to turn it to the left.
- Release the tether.
- Yes, Master.
Jolyne, do not take your eyes off
that Stand.
While it's in your sight,
it'll act like an obedient servant.
Though creepy,
it will prove useful to you.
But turn your back on it
for a second, and…
Fuck…
Who would have thought that was an attack?
Jolyne, Anastasia…
Don't let it out of your sight!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter